Children’s use of social media is a problem.
儿童使用社交媒体是个问题。
That doesn’t mean it should be stopped.
这并不意味着就应该加以禁止。
While younger children should not be on platforms where 13 is the minimum age, it is neither practical nor desirable to imagine a world in which teenagers are prevented from accessing the platforms and messaging systems that the adults around them use to organise their lives.
虽然年龄更小的孩子不应该使用最低年龄要求为13岁的平台，但青少年身边的成年人用平台和通讯系统来安排生活，设想一个不让青少年使用这些平台和系统的世界，既不现实，也不可取。
But the pleasure and stimulation that people of all ages find on their screens and smartphones must not blind us to the harm that spending time in this way can cause.
但是，各个年龄段的人从屏幕和智能手机上获得的乐趣和刺激，绝不能让我们对这样花时间可能造成的危害视而不见。
The finding that the alarmingly high rate of depression in British teenage girls is closely correlated to time spent on social media is extremely concerning.
研究发现，英国少女高得惊人的抑郁症患病率与她们花在社交媒体上的时间密切相关，这一发现令人极为担忧。
Research found that two in five girls are on social media for at least three hours a day—with half as many boys engaged to the same extent.
研究发现，五分之二的女孩每天使用社交媒体至少三小时，而男孩中达到同样程度的比例是女孩的一半。
More than a third of depressed girls have experienced online harassment.
在患抑郁症的女孩中，超过三分之一遭受过网络骚扰。
About half of affected girls suffered disrupted sleep, compared with 20% of depressed boys.
在患病的女孩中，约有一半睡眠受到干扰，相比之下，患抑郁症的男孩中这一比例为20%。
Although the research does not prove that social media causes depression, the importance of the finding that there is a connection should not be underestimated.
尽管这项研究并未证明社交媒体会导致抑郁症，但二者之间存在关联这一发现，其重要性不应低估。
Schools have done important work in communicating key messages about the risks of online abuse.
在传达有关网络侵害风险的关键信息方面，学校已经做了重要的工作。
But when it comes to broader questions about “screen time”, many professionals as well as parents are confused and uncertain.
但一谈到“屏幕时间”方面更宽泛的问题，许多专业人士和家长都感到困惑，心里没底。
The health secretary, Matt Hancock, wants official guidelines on time and age limits.
卫生大臣马特·汉考克希望出台有关时长限制和年龄限制的官方指南。
This idea has the virtue of simplicity, though some experts question its effects and call for a greater degree of differentiation, arguing that time online by itself is not a bad thing and it all depends on what you are doing.
这一想法的优点在于简单，不过一些专家质疑其效果，呼吁做出更细致的区分，他们认为，上网时间本身并不是坏事，一切都取决于你在做什么。
Also due this year is information commissioner Elizabeth Denham’s Age Appropriate Design Code, covering the use of children’s personal data.
今年预计还将出台信息专员伊丽莎白·德纳姆的《适龄设计规范》，该规范涉及儿童个人数据的使用。
Both initiatives are welcome.
这两项举措都值得欢迎。
But the government is playing catch-up.
但政府的行动已经滞后，现在是在努力追赶。
Statutory regulation of the digital media giants is long overdue.
对数字媒体巨头的法定监管早就该实行了。
The failure to protect children from data harvesting and targeted advertising thus far is as shocking as the lack of concern shown by the companies themselves with regard to children’s psychological health.
迄今为止都未能保护儿童免受数据采集和定向广告的侵害，这与这些公司本身对儿童心理健康缺乏关心一样令人震惊。
Of course, social media companies are not the source of all our ills, and can offer a too-easy target for politicians keen to divert attention from inadequately resourced schools and health services.
当然，社交媒体公司并非我们一切弊病的根源，而且有些政客急于把人们的注意力从资源不足的学校和医疗服务上转移开，对这些政客来说，社交媒体公司可能太容易成为攻击的靶子了。
There are other reasons for the rising incidence of depression in young people, with increasing pressure to succeed in education and in life more broadly—to be famous, beautiful, rich—often cited as a source of unhappiness or anxiety which can, if aggravated by other factors, and not managed, tip into ill health.
年轻人抑郁症发病率不断上升还有其他原因：要在学业上乃至整个人生中取得成功——要出名、要漂亮、要富有——这种压力与日俱增，常被列为不快乐或焦虑的一个根源；而如果其他因素使这种不快乐或焦虑加剧，又没有加以控制，就可能演变为疾病。
Safeguarding means more than the avoidance of physical threat.
保护儿童不只意味着避免身体上的威胁。